Guide to the Administrative Files of the Dean of the School of Education, Daniel E. Griffiths 1948-1985 (Bulk 1965-1983) RG 26.0.1 RG.26.0.1
New York University Archives
- Griffiths Container List
  - VP George H. Williams, 1965-1968 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Office of Assitant VP, undated (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Experimental Teaching Center, undated (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Reports, Budgets, Correspondence, Proposals and Projects, undated (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - ETC-DPP Manolakes, Stoddard, Nicholas, Sexton, Hester, undated (Box 136, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 343 0
  - TOBE, undated (Box 137, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 344 8
  - Duff, Philosophy of Research, Hill, undated (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Ms., Punch Cards, Presentation, Contracts, Conference, Correspondence, undated (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Thesis, Reports, Minutes, Agreements, undated (Box 138, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 345 5
  - General Correspondence: A-Z, 1963-1974 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 346 3
  - Petty Cash, Request for Checks, Placement, undated (Box 140, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 347 1
  - Committee of the Committees: Faculty Structure and Committee Functioning, 1957 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Rating Form, undated (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Personnel Policies: School of Ed, 1971 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Bylaws for the SENAP, 1979 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Report of the Special Committee on the School of Ed Curriculum, 1953 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Work of a Faculty Team, School of Ed, 1958-1959 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Policies Pertaining to Degree Requirements, 1958-1962 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Teacher Education at NYU: Report to NCATE, 1966 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Report of the NYU Program in Educational Administration and Supervision, 1966 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Report: The School's Role in Coming of Age in a Big City, 1962 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Report: Inquiry - Instruction - Service, 1962 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Application for Grant for Construction of Academic Facilitities, 1965 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Transparancies for Long-Range Planning Report to the Faculty, 1979 (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - Report on Long-Range Planning 1978-79 to 1985-85 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 348 9
  - Advisory Committee on the Future of the School, 1978 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Divisional Projections for the Report of the Future of the School, 1978 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - New York University Handbook, 1972 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - SENAP Publicity, undated (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Bermuda National Programme in Community Education, 1980 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Evaluation of Courses, 1976-1980 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - New York University Goals Conference, 1974 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Report: New Directions for the School of Education, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - NYU Promotional Speech, undated (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Academic Goals - NYU School of Education, undated (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Education, 1971 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Reflections - various copies, undated (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Scope, undated (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - Black Students at NYU, undated (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - Griffiths Blue Book, undated (Box 141, Folder 16)
  - Code Area (Black Book), undated (Box 142, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 349 7
  - Commission on Secondary Schools, undated (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Center for Economic Education, undated (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - CADEA, undated (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Visual Arts, undated (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - NDEA, undated (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - NEA, undated (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Sidney Roth, undated (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - IDS, undated (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - TEPS, undated (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Aging Institute for Study of, undated (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Report on Virgin Island Students, undated (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Emmanuel Hammer, undated (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Hofstra, undated (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - Housing, undated (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - Institute of Crippled and Disabled, undated (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - Int. Co-op Administration, undated (Box 142, Folder 17)
  - Journal of Ed. Sociology, undated (Box 142, Folder 18)
  - Iven Memy, undated (Box 142, Folder 19)
  - Personnel, undated (Box 143, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 352 1
  - Dean Pollock, undated (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Portman's Linguistics Project, undated (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rican Center, undated (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Puerto Rican Proposal, undated (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Dr. Milton Schwebel, undated (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Second Chance University, undated (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Speigel, C.D.: College Union Administration, undated (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Stillman College, undated (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Poverty Programs, undated (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - ISE Journal, undated (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Rulin Plan, undated (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Terminations, 1966 (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Kappa Phi Kappa, undated (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Committee Reports, undated (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - UCEA Files, 1958-1962 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 353 9
  - UCEA FIles, 1959 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 354 7
  - Educational Administration Quarterly, undated (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - NYS Doctoral Program Review, 1980 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Teacher Mobility in NYC, undated (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Operational Taxonomic Units, undated (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Files, undated (Box 146, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 355 4
  - Miscellaneous Files, undated (Box 147, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 356 2
  - NYC Study - "Dead", undated (Box 148, Folder 2)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 357 0
  - PEA Presenation of NYC, undated (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Transparancy Material, 1964 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 2 of NYC Study, undated (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Bue and White Box, undated (Box 149, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 358 8
  - Dean Griffiths, 1960-1967 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - School of Ed - Weekly Reports: Schwebel, undated (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Weekly Reports, undated (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Budget for 1964-65, 1965 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Requests for Released Time for Academic Year, 1964-1965 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - School of Ed Budget, 1965-1966 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Division Heads, 1965 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Recruitment for 1966-67 positions, 1965-1966 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - School of Ed: California, 1966 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Trip to Chicago, Madison, Milwaukee, Ann Arbor, 1965 (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Meeting with Cremin, Tyler, Gage, Jamor, 1965 (Box 149, Folder 14)
  - Meeting with Daniel Danes, 1965 (Box 149, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Members Liable to Be Moved Away from NYU, 1965 (Box 149, Folder 16)
  - Distinguished Professorships, 1965 (Box 149, Folder 17)
  - Publications Program, 1965 (Box 149, Folder 18)
  - Analysis of Course Inventories, 1966 (Box 149, Folder 19)
  - Merrifield, Philip R., undated (Box 149, Folder 20)
  - Psych Chairmanship Candidates, undated (Box 149, Folder 21)
  - Anderson Material - Gallatin College, 1961 (Box 149, Folder 22)
  - Anderson, Walter A.: Report on Education in Federal Republic of Germany, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 23)
  - Self-Directed Learning Project, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 24)
  - Committee of Eleven, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 25)
  - NYU Ideas, 1961 (Box 149, Folder 26)
  - CAL, 1961-1962 (Box 149, Folder 27)
  - Class Materials, undated (Box 149, Folder 28)
  - T.C. Office of Doctoral Studies, undated (Box 149, Folder 29)
  - Daniel Griffiths - Personnel, undated (Box 149, Folder 30)
  - Blue and White Box #2, 1965-1971 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 359 6
  - Center for Urban Education, undated (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - APEX: Meeting with Dr. Shilen, 1967 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Meeting, 1966 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - APEX Project, undated (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - APEX II: Proposal to Ford Foundation, 1965 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - APEX: Robertson Project, undated (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - NDEA: Application, undated (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - NDEA: Title IV, 1969-1970 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - NDEA: Wagner, Sigrid, 1972-1973 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - NDEA: New Fllows, 1969 -1975 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - NDEA Fellowships: Communication with Applicants, undated (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - NDEA, 1971 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - Title IV (DEAD), undated (Box 150, Folder 14)
  - NDEA Fellowships, undated (Box 150, Folder 15)
  - NDEA Title IV Holders (School of Ed), 1973-1974 (Box 150, Folder 16)
  - Project APEX - Promotional Material, undated (Box 150, Folder 17)
  - NDEA Wohlkin, Adrienne M., 1972-1973 (Box 150, Folder 18)
  - Rubenstein, Sherry Ann, undated (Box 150, Folder 19)
  - Mahan, Brian Fisher, undated (Box 150, Folder 20)
  - NDEA Followship - Title IV Applicants, 1972-1973 (Box 150, Folder 21)
  - NDEA Title IV Holders, 1970-1971 (Box 150, Folder 22)
  - NDEA - Fellowships Communication with Department Heads, undated (Box 150, Folder 23)
  - Alphabetized Gen. Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 360 4
  - Academic Freedom for PS Teachers, undated (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - DEG Correspondence, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - DEG Correspondence, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - DEG Correspondence, 1965 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Gen. Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Attitudes and Perceoptions of Desirable Traits and Behaviors of Teachers, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Daniel E. Griffiths - Jerome S. Coles and Recreation Center, 1980-1981 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 264 8
  - Dental Center Material, undated (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - NYU Master Communications Plan, 1983-1992 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Kansas, undated (Box 153, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 265 5
  - National Commission Excellence in Administration of America's Schools, undated (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - UCEA National Commission: Certification, Preparation, In-Service, Concept, undated (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Danforth, undated (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Dental Review Committee Meeting, 1983 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Confidential External Review Comm. Report on the NYU College of Dentistry, undated (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Dental Center Material, undated (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - University Council for Education Administration, undated (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Dental File, undated (Box 154, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 283 8
  - Coles Sports and Recreation Center, 1980-1981 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications, undated (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - New School of Education - Educational Specifications Worksheets, undated (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Ed. Specifications Worksheets: Book 3, undated (Box 155, Folder 2)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 284 6
  - Ed. Specifications Worksheets: Book 4, undated (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Ed. Specifications Worksheets: Book 5, undated (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Ed. Specifications Worksheets: Book 6, undated (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Budge Comparison Sheets, 1958-1965 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 285 3
  - Arawark, undated (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Galleys as Returned to Interstate (Xerox copy), undated (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Galleys edited by Griffiths, McCarthy, undated (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - DEG Professional Tapes, Slide Presentations, undated (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Marmaroneck Public Schools - 10 Reels, undated (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Study Skills Meeting - Marmoroneck - 2 reels, undated (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Background Tape (Tuesday Morning), undated (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Annual Meeting of Marmoroneck, 1958 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Research Seminar, 1963 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - 5 1/2 min. version - Jeff. School Film, undated (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - "Wattsie", OCEA, 1961 (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - PR Slides, Sets 1-3, undated (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - UCEA (4 reels), 1959 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 286 1
  - NYU Wisdom Bank, "New Frontiers in Ed", undated (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Slides on Paradigm - Griffiths, Teachers, College Columbia, Z boxes, undated (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Daniel E. Griffiths - "The Use of Theory in Administration", 1960 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Conference: Dean Griffiths, 1971 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Intro of Principals to the Materials for Principals Workshop, undated (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Mr. Kelly, Mrs. Gray, Music Festival, Stolen Jackets, undated (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Reel, undated (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - University of Michigan Microfilm, undated (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Chemical Explosions, undated (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - D.E. Griffiths CAL Tape Recording, 1962 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Tuesday Morning Background Recording, undated (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Chemistry Class Explosion, undated (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - New Unused Slides, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Formerly Used Slides (2 boxes), undated (Box 157, Folder 15)
  - CAL Flimstrip, 1962 (Box 157, Folder 16)
  - Vice Dean Payne, undated (Box 158, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 287 9
  - Faculty: Aims of the School, undated (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Grace Church School, undated (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - NYU - Digest of the Reports of Officers, 1948-1949 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Marolakes Committee, undated (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Digest of the Reports of Officers, 1949-1951 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Education Violet Review, 1974 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - General Theory of Education, undated (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Thesis - Organization, undated (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - New Careers, 1967 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Giles Project, undated (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Project APEX, undated (Box 159, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 288 7
  - APEX, undated (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Clinic for Learning, 1966 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Gallatin College, undated (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Dockets - Incomplete, undated (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Dockets Under Review, undated (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - IDS, undated (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Developmental Studies, undated (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Grades and Attendance - History of Education in Recent Times, 1964 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Grades and Attendance - Study, 1964-1965 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Grades and Attendance: Problems of Secondary Education, undated (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - 888 Grades and Attendance, undated (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - E-24.0012 - Grades and Attendance, undated (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - ETA-I Grades and Attendance, undated (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - ETA-II Grades and Attendance, 1966-1967 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - ETA-III Grades and Attendance, 1963-1966 (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - AASA: General, 1969-1970 (Box 159, Folder 17)
  - AASA: Hot Line, 1969-1970 (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - AASA: School Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - AAUP, undated (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Association, undated (Box 159, Folder 21)
  - Center for Economical Education, undated (Box 159, Folder 22)
  - Project APEX, undated (Box 159, Folder 23)
  - Center for Field Research, undated (Box 159, Folder 24)
  - Center for International Studies, undated (Box 159, Folder 25)
  - Central Administration, undated (Box 159, Folder 26)
  - Dissertation Comm., undated (Box 159, Folder 27)
  - ETFP Project: Lonsdale, undated (Box 160, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 289 5
  - Faculty Activities, undated (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Appointments, undated (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Club, NYU, undated (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Faculty List - School of Ed., undated (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Research Seminar, undated (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Retirements, undated (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Sabbatical Leaves, undated (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Retirement Age, undated (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Ford Foundation, undated (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - Housing, undated (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - ISR, 1968-1969 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - Karr, N.A. President, undated (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Bruce Kelly Memorial, undated (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - Study for Library Service, undated (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - NCPEA Conference, 1968 (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - Third Annual Convention of the NCPEA, 1968 (Box 160, Folder 17)
  - NDEA Institute for Student Personnel Spec., undated (Box 160, Folder 18)
  - NYU Mental Health, undated (Box 160, Folder 19)
  - NYU Camp, undated (Box 160, Folder 20)
  - NYU Seminar (Redefer), undated (Box 160, Folder 21)
  - Ombudsman, Prof. London, undated (Box 160, Folder 22)
  - Office Procedures, undated (Box 160, Folder 23)
  - Office Salaries, undated (Box 160, Folder 24)
  - Office Special Projects, undated (Box 160, Folder 25)
  - Opportunities Program, undated (Box 160, Folder 26)
  - School of Education Policies, undated (Box 160, Folder 27)
  - Admin. Policies in the School of Ed, 1968-1969 (Box 160, Folder 28)
  - Polices to be Developed, undated (Box 160, Folder 29)
  - Policy Code 407, undated (Box 160, Folder 30)
  - Policy Petty Cash, undated (Box 160, Folder 31)
  - Policy / Vac. Personnel, undated (Box 160, Folder 32)
  - Policy Publicity, undated (Box 160, Folder 33)
  - Policy - Use of Alumni, undated (Box 160, Folder 34)
  - Policy Procedures, undated (Box 160, Folder 35)
  - Faculty Policy - general, undated (Box 160, Folder 36)
  - Legal Procedures, undated (Box 160, Folder 37)
  - Policy Statements, undated (Box 160, Folder 38)
  - Policy Sabbatical Leaves, undated (Box 160, Folder 39)
  - Policy Accident Theft, undated (Box 160, Folder 40)
  - Faculty Policy By-Laws, undated (Box 160, Folder 41)
  - Post-Doc. Fell. In Res., undated (Box 160, Folder 42)
  - Registration, 1968 (Box 160, Folder 43)
  - Registration / Mail Proceed., undated (Box 160, Folder 44)
  - Registration - summer, 1968 (Box 160, Folder 45)
  - Intercession Registration, 1969-1970 (Box 160, Folder 46)
  - Rented Space for Projects, undated (Box 160, Folder 47)
  - Safety Committee, Washington Square, undated (Box 160, Folder 48)
  - Student Activities, undated (Box 160, Folder 49)
  - Sudent Faculty Comm., undated (Box 160, Folder 50)
  - Summer Sessions, undated (Box 160, Folder 51)
  - Taggart Comm., undated (Box 160, Folder 52)
  - Teacher Coprs, undated (Box 160, Folder 53)
  - UCEA, undated (Box 160, Folder 54)
  - UCEA Newsletter, undated (Box 160, Folder 55)
  - Undergraduate Student Council, undated (Box 160, Folder 56)
  - Virgin Islands Project, undated (Box 160, Folder 57)
  - Faculty Handbook, undated (Box 161, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 290 3
  - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Budget Adjustments, 1969-1970 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Adm. - Student Referral, undated (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Admission Reports, undated (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Information, undated (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Insurance, undated (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Medical Services, undated (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Salaries, undated (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Moving Authorizations, undated (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - King, Martin Luther - Scholarships Fund Comm., undated (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - Vocational Education, undated (Box 161, Folder 13)
  - Home Economics, Division of, undated (Box 161, Folder 14)
  - Mathematics Ed., Dept. of, undated (Box 161, Folder 15)
  - Science and Math, undated (Box 161, Folder 16)
  - Educational Research Services, 1968-1969 (Box 161, Folder 17)
  - OERS Research and Training Projects, undated (Box 161, Folder 18)
  - Educational Technology, Committee on, undated (Box 161, Folder 19)
  - NYU Charter and By-Laws, undated (Box 161, Folder 20)
  - Advertisements, undated (Box 161, Folder 21)
  - Xerox, undated (Box 161, Folder 22)
  - Advertisements, 1968-1969 (Box 161, Folder 23)
  - Summer Sessions Advertisements, undated (Box 161, Folder 24)
  - Reactions Session - All-Day Faculty Meeting, 1969-1970 (Box 161, Folder 25)
  - Annual Awareds Dinner, 1969 (Box 161, Folder 26)
  - Baccalaureata Receptions, 1968-1969 (Box 161, Folder 27)
  - Bureau of Conference FAC I, undated (Box 161, Folder 28)
  - Conferences Promotions, 1968-1969 (Box 161, Folder 29)
  - All Day Faculty, undated (Box 161, Folder 30)
  - Code 407: Approved, 1967-1968 (Box 161, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Lists, 1968-1969 (Box 161, Folder 32)
  - Loeb Student Center, 1969-1970 (Box 161, Folder 33)
  - Loeb Reservations, undated (Box 161, Folder 34)
  - Flaver Fund, undated (Box 161, Folder 35)
  - Loeb Billings, undated (Box 161, Folder 36)
  - New Faculty Reception, undated (Box 161, Folder 37)
  - Faculty Reception Work Folder, undated (Box 161, Folder 38)
  - Photographic Bureau Requisitions, undated (Box 161, Folder 39)
  - Elliot Minenberg, undated (Box 161, Folder 40)
  - Deans Group Meetings, undated (Box 161, Folder 41)
  - Weekly Reports for Minenberg and Spinner, undated (Box 162, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 291 1
  - Lou Kleinman Weekly, undated (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Kellogg Foundation Boys Club, undated (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Day File, 1970 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Purchase Requisitions Completed - 6000 up, 1968-1970 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Purchase Requisitions Completed up to 59999, undated (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Flaver Fund Printouts, undated (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Elliot Minenberg - Personnel, 1968-1969 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - New Xerox Billings, undated (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Travel Worksheets (A), undated (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Travel Worksheets (M), undated (Box 162, Folder 11)